You said in the comments that
J and I would be a great match,
and I actually thought so too,
so I invited her on a date
and we
bought the Sonnenfensternness together.
We then met up in Berlin
and I
invited her on a date, and I think
you definitely liked that.
We're basically both one and the same
person.  We're both a bit
tanned, we could
actually be siblings, but of
course I also got roses
, because that's what a
gentleman does, and personality-wise we're a
perfect match, because we
're both kind of hilarious and I don't
know, we just have the
same sense of humor, we're just the same,
sorry.  And then we went to
Cookie Tür before the sun started shining
and of course treated ourselves to some
cookies.  And now,
sorry, am I the only one,
or are we the only ones, who
somehow didn't see this solar eclipse
?  Dude, I didn't
see anything.  We were feeling a bit
sweet, still in the park, spent some
time together and
it was generally a really great day.
Why does Loki have a fatter ass
than me?  Take a look at this.  Bomb
[laughter]
such a fat ass.  Sorry.  E
Juli just had to go
home at some point, but of course I hope there will be
a second date.